So, this is pretty much a zero out, 21, 22.
Okay.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Aye.
Eastern.
Thanks, Mike.
Nine.
They would strike from May and claim for Pitzkola G.R.D.A.
Resolving.
In the amount of $26,890 and $73 for fiscal year, 21,22.
So, Mayor members of the Council in your packets, there is a document that explains the background of this particular invoice and gives a summation of what the invoice was for.
This was for services and disbursements incurred from June 1st through June 30.
So, this would be.
the final bill for DWT through last fiscal year, and on that particular
invoice it included efforts focusing on the preparation and presentation at the
June 10th Town Hall, as well as the assisted us in filing a motion to intervene in the
first investigation into the transparency of GRDA's Formula Rake Protocols on June 15th.
I'll lock the document.
Good.
We keep those, keep those coming fromitterD to him.
Motion to prendre.
Second?
Second.
Second, Mister.
Second ofpoke.
Second, brief.
Second?
Second.
Second?. würde. taco. zitio.
Second.нь. paranth. Intern.风. frost. los. Ner.
or his designated design, notice to proceed.
I don't see Robert's.
Do you see this last one?
This is our last one.
Now, we should investigate.
Or, it was in council, so we have to approve it.
We approve this as councilman, but not as in this way.
Most of you approve?
Second.
Is that Parker?
Hi.
Sandra.
I understand.
Ward of six-month contract at review of all bits of missions and recommendations for concrete
material C22-39, concrete sand C22-40, and aggregate rock C22-38, authorized
city manager his days in the.
Designed notice to proceed is recommended by staff upon the submission of all required documents.
We have about six months.
We didn't really feel like our materials.
Benders would want to commit to one year.
From where's there?
There.
surprise of the grace, actually, because a lot of the matters, first of all,
did you know I did?
I did.
I took advantage of this ability to up the search arms on fuel.
And so we did got it.
I took it right behind.
I took it through.
Second.
Sumber.
All right.
E-step.
Circle.
All right.
Davis.
Parker.
Thank you.
12.
New business.
Any, which is a residence in the posting of this agenda, it could not be anticipated prior
to the time of posting.
13.
Trustee community announcements.
14.
General.
Motion.
Second.
Double.
Right.
E-step.